Guide to the Fernando Alegria Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 3. Manuscripts by others
  - Marcus Rodriguez, Louis. California style: tms, 1990, 1 v. (141 p.) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Memet, Jose Maria. Amanecer sin dioses: tms, 1996-1998, and supporting documents, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Mann, Patricio. El desorden en un cuerno de niebla: tms, 1990 Nov. 16, 1 v. (361 p.) + 1 ans (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Manriquez, Sebastian. La carta a Kissinger: novela: tms, n.d., 1 v. (272 p.) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Merino, Luis. Vision del compositor Juan Orrego-Smith. -- p. 5-105. -- In Revista Musical Chilena. -- Vol. 32, no. 142-144 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Merino, Luis. Para leer a Arguendas: a proposito del libro Cultura popular y forma novelesca de Martin Lienhard: tms, 1986 Mar. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Merino, Luis y Hiroyasu Tomoeda. La danza de la degollación del Inca. -- p. 143-159 1992 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Molina, Carlos M. Poems (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Montes, Gregory. The bridge of Barajas: review draft [1 of 2], ca. 1995, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Montes, Gregory. The bridge of Barajas: review draft [2 of 2], ca. 1995, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Morgada, Jose Miguel. Santiago de noche: tms, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Muñoz, Diego. Las tres etapas de la lirica Nerudiana. -- Santiago: Ediciones Lastarria, ca. 1979, 2 copies (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Murillo-Martin, Sonia and Carolina Moroder-Murillo. Los años intensos de Fernando Alegria: tms, 1992 July 31 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Navarro, R.J. Los chilenos en California en 1849-1850: tms (photocopy), n.d., 64 p. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Neira Gonzalez, María. Señales de vida y de muerte: tms, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Neruda, Pablo. Art of birds: tms (photocopy) / by Pablo Neruda; trans. by Hadas Marcus n.d. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Neruda, Pablo. Typed excerpt from unidentified ms. -- p. 31-36 n.d. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Neruda, Pablo. Spain in the heart = España en el corazon: photocopy, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Noel, Tomas Uruyoén. The postponed picnic: tms, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Nuñez, Guillermo. Letter, Paris, to una querida compañera, 1979 Feb. 16 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Nunn, Frederick. Latinamericanidad from Encuentro to Quincentennial: tms, n.d., 52 p. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Nunn, Frederick M. On the role of the military in Twentieth Century Latin America: the Mexican case: tms, 1984 May 23 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Nunn, Frederick M. One year in the life of Augusto Pinochet: tms, ca. 1984, 17 p. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - [Oddo], Guillermo. Desde siempre: tms, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Ortega, B[ertin]. El campo como Utopia: partial tms: pp. 53-96, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Ortega, Bertin. La novela proletaria en Mexico en los años treinta: tms, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Ortega, Julio. Vallejo: la poética de la subversion. -- p. 267-296. -- In Hispanic Review. -- Vol. 50, no. 3 1982 Summer (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Perez, Rosa Perelmuter. La estructura retórica de la Respuesta a Sor Filotea. -- p. 147-158. -- In Hispanic Review. --- Vol. 51, no. 2 1983 Spring (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Perezdiaz, Roberto. El papalote: tms, n.d., 59 p. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - El Perro Olivares: transcription: tms, ca. 1975 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Poemas by various authors (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - [Poems]: tms, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Poniatowski, Elena. La casita de sololoi. -- p. 133-143. -- In De noche vienes. -- Mexico: Editorial Grijalbo, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Prado, Marcela. Diario de mis lecturas: tms, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Prado, Marcela. Ines Echeverria de Larrain: tms, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Quesada, Roberto. El humano y la diosa: novela: tms, ca. 1996, 1 v. (162 p.) (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Quesada, Roberto. Nunca entres por Miami: novela: tms, ca. 1997, 1 v. (157 p.) (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Rafael. Testimonio: tms, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Ramirez-Bitschkus, Immo. Poems: tms, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Rebollada, Enrique. Tres dialogos profundos: tms, 1961, 1 v. with hand-carved wooden boards (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Rela, Walter. Celebraciones teatrales y fiestas en el Paraguay colonial. -- Montevideo: Universidad de la Republica, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Rigoli, Juan. Los Borges de Heraclito: tms, n.d., 28 p. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Rodriguez, Ileana. Various tms, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Rodriguez, Louis Marcus. Hemingway's suitcase: tms, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Rodriguez, Louis Marcus. Various tms, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Rodriguez, Marlowe. I am: tms, 1988, 1 p. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Rodriguez, Osvaldo. Conversación con Fernando Alegria: tms, 1985 Feb. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Roggiano, Alfredo. Destino personal y destino nacional en el Martin Fierro. -- p. 219-230. -- In Revista Iberoamericana. -- Vol. 40, no. 87-88 1974 Apr. - Sept. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Rosales, Vincente Perez. California adventure 1947 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Ruiz-Tagle, Carlos. Aguafuerte de Nicanor Parra: tms, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Sabat Ercasty, Carlos. Himno al joven de la esparanza, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Schopf, Federico. Modernismo y modernidad: tms, n.d., 7 p. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Schopf, Federico. Reconocimiento de Gabriela Mistral. -- p. 152-171. -- In EW. -- No. 248 1982 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Semprún Donahue, Moraima de. La figura del heroe en la obra de Fernando Alegria: tms, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Rodriguez, Marcus. ¡Buenos dias, California!: novela: tms, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Slavinsky, Barbara. Hermeneutics of Clarice Lispector's fiction: a dialogue study toward an aesthetic and ethical exegesis: tms, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Smith, David Carlson. The Chilean spring: screenplay: tms, 1991, 112 p. (cy 1) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Smith, David Carlson. The Chilean spring: screenplay: tms, 1991, 112 p. (cy 2) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Stuart, Alejandro. Un brindis de Año Nuevo, 1994 Jan., 3 p.; illus. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Includes illustration of musician and image of soldier.
  - Subercaseaux, Bernardo. Identidades politicas y vocas culturales: tms, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Tamayo Vargas, Augusto. Literatura Peruana y Literatura Brasileña a traves de los siglos. -- (Publicaciones del Instituto .... San Marcos, no. 3). -- Lima: El Instituto, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Teillier, Jorge. Muertes y maravilla & Nidos de antaño: tms, 1978-1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Torres, Jorge. Poemas encontrados y otros pre-textos. -- Valdivia, Chile: Ediciones Paginadura, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Valencia, Juan. El mundo es para todos: tms, 1975, 3 p. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Valencia, Maria, Jaime Dvor, Carlos Sotomayor. Salon de Agosto n.d. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Vasquez, G.L. Peruvian radicalism and the Sendero Luminoso. -- p. 197-217. -- In Journal of Political and Military Sociology. -- Vol. 21 1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Velasco L., Eugenio. Expulsion: tms, 1976 Aug. 6 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Villafañe León, Ines. Daring: tms, 1998 Nov. 19 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Villafañe León, Ines. La perdida de Alah: tms, 1997 July (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Villafañe León, Ines. The secret: tms, 1998 Feb. 2 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Villafañe León, Ines. El terremoto: tms, 1998 Sept. 18 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Villegas, Juan. Teatro chileno y afianzamiento de los secretos medias. -- p. 306-318. -- In Ideologies and Literature. -- No. 17 1983 Sept. - Oct. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Whitman, Walt. Pasto de llamas: traducción de Pablo Neruda: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Zaillian, Steven. Schlinder's list: screenplay: draft, 1993 Jan. 31, 1 v. (151 p.) (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Zapata-Whelan, Carol M. With faces turn'd sideways: Walt Whitman and Ruben Dario: partial tms, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Includes acs from author.
  - Dialogo disonante e ingrimo (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Garcilaso de la Vega and pastoral theory (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 10 preguntas irreverentes sobre los Placeres a Fernando Alegria: una especie de entrevista (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - 39 poems: tms [possibly by Jorge Argueta] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - 54 poems: tms / by Jorge [Argueta] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Poems dedicated to Neruda n.d. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Untitled tms of poetry: tms, n.d., 1 v. (48 p.) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Untitled draft of dissertation on Roque Dalton: tms [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Untitled draft of dissertation on Roque Dalton: tms [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Untitled draft of dissertation on Roque Dalton: tms [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Bachelet Martinez, Fernando. Politica norteamericana hacia Chile desde septiembre de 1970. Alcances y proyecciones. El peso ideologico: tms (photocopy), 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Barraza, Eduardo. El discurso de la historia en la narrativa del 38: tms, 1993 Apr. 8 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Caceres Milnes, Andres. La marginalidad en dos novelas de Fernando Alegria. -- Thesis (M.L.) 1989, 1 v. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - De Erauso, Catalina. Vida i sucesos de la Monja Alferez: tms [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - De Erauso, Catalina. Vida i sucesos de la Monja Alferez: tms [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - De Erauso, Catalina. Vida i sucesos de la Monja Alferez: tms [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Dominguez, Delia. Impulso: poema de contrapunto: tms, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Dominguez, Delia. Señales de una poesia mestiza en el paralelo 40 sur: tms, n.d., 1 v. (spiral bound) (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Elsacca, Theodoro. Navios fantasmales: tms, ca. 1992, 1 v. (spiral bound) (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Paredes, Jose. Desde el fuego: poemas selectos, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Poems: tms, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Rojas, Gonzalo. La palabra: tms, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Silva, Alegria. Para crecer un arbol: tms, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - de Rokha, Pablo. Canto de fuego a China popular 1963 Dec. (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Kessler, Stephen. Man with an ax 1981 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Series 4. Subject files
  - Address list (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Aguirre-Tupper, Isidora (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - ALA [Agencia Latinoamericana]: articles [1 of 2] (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - ALA [Agencia Latinoamericana]: articles [2 of 2] (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Alarcon, Francisco X. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Reviews of works by (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Allende, Isabel (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Allende, Salvador (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Allende, Salvador (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Allende, Salvador: 10 años despues = 10 years after (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Allende: a novel. Correspondence with Stanford University Press, reviews, publicity (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Andean pact (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Anthologies (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Archibald, Priscilla (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Art (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Arte (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Arte Publico Press (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Asturias, Miguel A. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Avant Garde / Latin America vanguardia (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Ayesa, Guillermo (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Ban of instruction (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Barrientos, Raul (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Bibliografia (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Bibliografia de la poesia chilena en Atenea (1924-1950) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Bibliografia de la poesia chilena en Atenea (Enero 1950-June 1962) (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bibliography (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Biblioteca Ayacucho (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Bolivia (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Borges, Jorge Luis (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Bravo, Roberto. Latin America: poetry and song: class materials (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Fundacion Roberto Bravo (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Burciaga, Cecilia (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - California: presencia de Chile (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Canciones (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Casa de las Americas (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Centre Georges Pompidou (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Centro America Literaria 1948 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Centro Cultural Fernando Alegria (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Centro de Estudios Literarios (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Centro Lautaro (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Chacabucco (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Chile 1973 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Chile during the coup (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Chile. Index of historic individuals (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Chile. Index of pioneers (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Chile-H@listserve.tamu.edu (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Chile, tourist information (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Chile - California Foundation (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Chilean artists (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Chilean poetry collection (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Columbus, Christopher, article re: 1997 Oct. 4 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Comision Chilena de Derechos Humanos (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Conferences (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Congressional Record (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Crane, Hart (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Crane, Hart. Brooklyn bride [1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Crane, Hart. Brooklyn bride [2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Cuba (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Cuba: Encuentro La Soberanía de los Pueblos, 1981 Sept. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Dalton, Roque (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Dance (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - de Rokha, Pablo (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Discursos Español (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Falu, Eduardo (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Film (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Flyers (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation. Employment position announcement: tms, 1999 Feb. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Fundacion Biblioteca Ayacucho (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Galaz Vivar, Alicia (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Ginsberg, Allen (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Guerra, Lucia (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Hispania Books Distributors, Inc. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Homenaje a Fernando Alegria, Stanford University = Homage to Fernando Alegria, Stanford University, 1988 Nov. 11-12 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Huidobro, Vincente (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Identity Politics (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Interview: Conversaciones con Fernando Alegria / Carla Maria Faini 1990 Oct. 30 & 1990 Nov. 14 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Jews (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Jofre, Manuel A. (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - LASSA (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Lastra, Pedro [1 of 2] (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Lastra, Pedro [2 of 2] (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Latin American News Service (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Leal, Luis (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Lectures 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Lectures: announcements (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Lecture outlines: 20th Century Latin America (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Letelier, Isanel Margarita (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Letelier, Orlando [1 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Letelier, Orlando [2 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Literatura del exilio (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Literatura en el exilio = Literature in exile (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Literatura en el exilio: antologia, The Crossing Press, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Literatura en el exilio: censura y auto-censura (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Literatura en el exilio: auto-censura (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Literatura en el exilio [1977] Mar. 3 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Literatura en el exilio 1977 June (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Literatura Latina Americana: cursos: Fromm Institute (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Literatura Mexicana Contemporánea (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Literatura Peruana (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Literature and revolution in Latin America [1 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Literature and revolution in Latin America [2 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Literature and revolution in Latin America [3 of 3] (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Gabriel Garcia Marquez' Love in the time of cholera (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - McCracken Papers. Letters, 1849 Aug., photocopies (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - McCracken Papers. Cartas - Diario de McCracken: USA marinero en Talcahuano [1 of 2], photocopies (Box 45, Folder 6)
    originals in Bancroft Library, Univ. of California, Berkeley.
  - McCracken Papers. Cartas - Diario de McCracken: USA marinero en Talcahuano [2 of 2], photocopies (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Memory (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Mexico / Texas: maps (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Mistral, Gabriela (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Mistral, Gabriela: Nueva novela chilena, etc. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Mistral, Gabriela. Americas, poemas, fotos (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Mistral, Gabriela. Discovery (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Mitos = Myths (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Monreal, Andres (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Monterey County Literary Alliance. Open house introductions (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Mormons (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Mormons (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Music (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - National Endowment for the Arts. Proposed policy panelists (including Alegria): tms, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Neruda, Pablo (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Neruda, Pablo (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Neruda, Pablo (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Neruda, Pablo (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Neruda, Pablo. Notas para '95 y seminario (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Neruda, Pablo. Recortes, carta de Ricardo Latcham = Clippings, letter from Ricardo Latcham (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Neruda, Pablo. Residencias, etc. = Residences, etc. (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Neruda - Huidobro: Polemica: Huidobro - de Rokha (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - NEW-LABT [New Latin American Book Trade] (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Novela Hispanoamericana contemporanea: ms y otros [1 of 2], n.d. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Novela Hispanoamericana contemporanea: ms y otros [2 of 2], n.d. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Nueva historia de la novela Hispaniamericano, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Papeles politicos = Political papers (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Parra, Nicanor (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Parra, Violeta (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Parra, Violeta. Violeta made: radio series (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Paz, Octavio (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Peron, Juan (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Picasso, Pablo (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Picasso y Neruda seminario (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Pinochet Ugarte, Agusto (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Pinto, Ines (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Poesia - Canción = Poetry / Song (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Poesia - Canción: Poesía Hispano Americana contemporánea (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Poesia - Canción: Poesía popular (oral) Salvadoreña = Popular (oral) Salvadoran poetry (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Poesia - Canción: Poetry in song symposium (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Poesia - Canción: Songs and poems project (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Poesia Chilena = Chilean poetry (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Poesia, Chilóe: clandestina y otras [1 of 3] 1973 - 1977 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Poesia, Chilóe: clandestina y otras [2 of 3] 1973 - 1977 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Poesia, Chilóe: clandestina y otras [3 of 3] 1973 - 1977 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Posada del Angel (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Postcards (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Premio Internacional de Literatura Latinoamericana y del Caribe (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Premio Lautaro (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Premio Nacional de Literatura (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Premio Nacional de Literatura (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Premio Romulo Gallegos (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Premio Romulo Gallegos 1993 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Press release 1971 Apr. 5 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Programs (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Programs (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Programs (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Programs (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Programs (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Proyecto: Colleccion Nueva Narrativa Latinamericana = Project: New Latin American narrative collection (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Proyecto Il Bosco (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Proyecto: Revision critica de la poesia chilena contemporanea = Project: Critical revision of contemporary Chilean poetry (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Publicity (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Readings (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Readings (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Realismo magico: 100 años de soledad. Gabriel Garcia Marquez: discurso Nobel (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Rencoret, David (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Report on research (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Reviews (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Reviews (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Reviews (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Revista del Pedagogico (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Rodriguez, Marlowe (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Rodriguez Reeves, Rosa (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Roger Lee Associates. Promotional booklet (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Rubicon Tahoe (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Rulfo, Juan (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Sender, Ramon J. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Small presses (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Spanish-American novel (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University. Report of the Housing Task Force: tms, 1999 Aug. 13 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Sueldos, Fernando Alegria (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - SUNY Buffalo. Council on International Studies (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Taller para Fernando Alegria = Workshop for Fernando Alegria (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Task Force on Hispanic American Arts (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Teatro = Theater (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - El Teatro de la Esperanza (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Teillier, Jorge (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Theater. Zoot suit: program (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Torturadores de la Junta Fascista en Chile = Torturers of the fascist junta in Chile (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Trujillo, Carlos A. (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Vargas Llosa, Mario (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Viaje a Chile = Trip to Chile, 1987 Aug. 6 - Sept. 6 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Western Institute for Social Research (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Western Institute for Social Research documents (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Women novelists, Chile. Olano Campo, Nora. Gagarines: tms, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Women novelists, Chile. Sanchez Ferrán, Tania. Harry Belevan: lo fantastico en torno a la posmodernidad: tms, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Women novelists of Chile (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - World Press. Testimonial letters (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Art (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Flyers (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Theater (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Diaz de Villegas, Jose Luis (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Series 5. Notebooks
  - Address book, n.d., 1 v.; boards missing (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Address book, n.d., 1 v. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Telephone / addresses, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Addresses, n.d., 1 v.; disbound (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Allende: cuaderno no. 1: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; gray boards (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Allende (copiado): notebook, n.d., 1 v.; black boards (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Allende: notepad, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Allende: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; blue boards (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Allende: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; aquamarine boards (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Allende - Roque Dalton - Neruda (Preguntas): notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Analysis de "La Barcarola": notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Analysis de cuentos: notepad, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Antologia y estudios de cuentos: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; aquamarine boards (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Aprendizaje de la rebeldia: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; gray boards (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Campaña Allende: notebook, 1964 Aug. - Sept., 1 v.; gray boards (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Chile: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; pink boards (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Chile y la Unidad Popular: notes, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Chilean poetry: notes, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Columbus and 3 ships of dreams: the self-discovery of America: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - El conquistador y su paje: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; brown boards (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - El conquistador y su paje [and other stories]: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; grey boards (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Cordillera, nos. 1-3: notebooks, n.d., 3 v.; grey boards (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Correspondencia de Recabarren y Guadalupe, no. 2: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; grey boards (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Cursos seminarios: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Los dias: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Una especie de memoria: cuaderno no. 1: notebook, 1977, 1 v.; red boards (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Una especie de memoria: cuaderno no. 2: notebook, 1977, 1 v.; disbound (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - El evangelio segun Cristian, el foto [?]: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; green boards (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Generación del 50: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Las historias de Berkeley: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; yellow boards (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Las historias de Berkeley: notebook, n.d., 1 v.; red boards (Box 53, Folder 9)